Today we're going to talk about how to pick out and care for a good celery plant.
This one right here, it looks pretty good.
It's got a plant in each little spot for the four pack.
You really want to look for that.
You don't want to buy one that's missing one.
It looks pretty green, there's no black spots or yellow on any of the leaves or anything.
That one looks really good right there.
This particular variety takes ninety to one hundred and twenty days to fully mature.
So you want to get them started pretty early in the season.
You have to plant these in full sun and you have to water them.
Don't forget about watering them.
It's very important that you water them, at least once a day, or every two days.
You can use any basic fertilizer.
Miracle-Gro fertilizer is going to be good for just about anything.
It's going to make them a lot bigger.
It should help them grow faster.
You definitely want to look at the tags on these because it's going to tell you how long it's going to take for them to grow and how much space you should put in between them.
This one says about six to eight inches in between.
So they're going to get a little big so you want to give them a little bit of room to grow.
And you can plant them in any kind of basic potting mix or garden soil.
If you're going to put them in the ground you definitely want to use soil, if you're going to put them in a container, use a good potting mix.